Hiring a trusted realtor from the start is very important to get your property sold.
Here are a few examples.
181 Meisner Avenue, this homeowner hired two different realtors for way over a year to try to sell the property.
When they were unsuccessful, the homeowner came to me and I was able to relist for the same price,
hire professional photography and enroll the property in paid advertisement,
and get over 10 offers within 30 days on the market, selling it for 100% of the list price.
This is 327 Bregaud Avenue in Tottenville, Staten Island.
This homeowner also went through two different realtors.
This homeowner was a bit more savvy.
They noticed the unprofessionalism very early and fired both realtors within 45 days.
When the homeowner came to me, I was honest from the start.
I relisted the same price as it was prior and sold it for 96% of the list price within 6 weeks on the market.
This is 146 David Street.
The homeowner for this property went with the same realtor for over a year.
The situation with this was a little different.
It was a pre-foreclosure and required a seasoned agent that knew how to negotiate with the banks.
I was able to sell this property within 3 days on the market and got the foreclosure completely satisfied.
Please make sure you hire a trusted realtor from the start to get you the most money for your property.
You can reach me directly at 917-951-2142.